Fat cats are too easy. Go for the big fish.
Shooting Fish is a crime, comedy, romance film directed by Stefan Schwartz.
Two con artists hire an unwitting medical-school student
as a secretary for their latest scam.
Dylan, played by Dan Futterman.
Jez, played by Stuart Townsend.
Georgie, played by Kate Beckinsale.
Jez's Teacher, played by Rowena Cooper.
Samuel, played by Scott Charles.
Antonia, played by Antonia Corrigan.
Shooting Fish is a 1997 British romantic crime comedy film directed by Stefan Schwartz and co-written with Richard Holmes,
starring Dan Futterman and Stuart Townsend as two con men with Kate Beckinsale as their unwilling assistant.
The film was produced by Winchester Films and partly funded by National
Lottery money administered through the UK Arts Council.
Shooting Fish aimed to transfer well to international markets that were keen on
British films following the success of Four Weddings and a Funeral.
The film was released in the United Kingdom on 17 October
1997 and in the United States on 1 May 1998.
The film explores themes of london, england, chase, nightclub, fraud, liar.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.